No animals were harmed during the
production of this show.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
Turgut!
Attack!
Now!
Do not let them run!
Do not let them run away!
Stand behind.
Watch out, Goktug!
I cannot see anything!
Osman took my brother from me.
And I'll take his sheik from him!
I am here, my sheik!
Dervish Han!
Protect our sheik!
Hold on, my sheik.
Do not leave us.
Hang on.
Allah is right!
Soldiers!
Rush!
We stand back!
Tell Osman that...
...I'll take many more lives until
I take my sister back!
Sheik Edebali, are you okay?
The road is dangerous.
My soldiers will take you somewhere safe.
I'll bring a healer.
- You know where to take him.
- I do.
I'll inform Vizier.
Our plan worked.
The Greek fire we captured
in Sogut.
Use it when necessary.
However...
Our goal is to kick up a dust and
run away.
Do not hurt any innocents.
Don't worry.
Eyvallah (thank you) Osman Bey.
Where did they hide Boran,
Osman Bey?
The devil doesn't have one place.
I am going to make him pay for...
...every moment he captivated Boran.
Don't worry. We are going to find
Boran no matter what happens.
Inshallah (If Allah permits)
We'll find him.
Goktug.
Let Alps accompany
Hera to the castle.
As you order my Bey.
My Bey, Vizier is gathering Turkmens
in the inn.
Let's see what he is up to.
Let's go.
Let's go alps.
Turkmen Beys will be in the inn soon...
But, first of all, I wanted to see you.
Because I wanted to see the wisest...
...the nimblest.
Welcome, Gunduz Bey.
Thank you Vizier Alam-shah.
The reason I wanted to see you is...
...your brother Osman Bey.
What a valiant Bey, isn't he?
He is brave, he is warrior.
He is undefeatable.
...Rebel...
Lawless...
...disobeyer.
What are you trying to say?
Gunduz Bey.
This is the state tradition.
Like the two headed eagle.
One conquers, one is wise.
He sees the future.
Why are you not the Bey.
This is my father Ertugrul Ghazi's order.
My brother wanted the throne.
What I needed to do was to let him.
Why are you asking?
Now that Osman has the throne...
...you have the wise role.
Take care of your brother's step.
He pokes his nose in everywhere.
If my brother is poking his nose,
then it is necessary to do so for Kayis.
Our Bey shows us the aim,
we become an arrow and fly.
It is nice to see determined Beys are
protecting this land.
You are loyal to Osman.
One must be supported if he
strives for the Turk's benefits.
Of course.
Whoever strives for the Turk's benefits...
We always support them.
What about me?
Gaining the trust of such a Bey is...
...more important than anything for me.
Hadrat Vizier...
...we are the edge tribe of Seljuqs.
Of course we follow the Vizier
appointed by Seljuqs.
Good.
I want you to attend in
the assembly.
Let all the Beys see how lucky
Osman Bey to have you.
Not everyone has a mighty Bey
like you beside them.
As you say.
Inegol Castle.
If a soldier fails to kill...
He doesn't deserve...
...living.
- My dear friend.
- Kosses.
If you give me one more bad news...
Contrarily, the news are good.
Vizier Alam-shah wanted me to stop Edebali
from going to Konya.
Hadrat Vizier wanted me to notify
you in particular that...
...Edebali will not die.
However, he may be wounded in the
way of Konya.
Is that so?
I wonder what kind of a plan
Vizier Alam-shah is setting.
I'll do as Vizier says.
Our game has to be convincing, right?
Bring me the armor.
This is going to protect me from arrows.
I did what he asked.
Now he will do what I ask.
He'll bring Mari back.
Nice.
This is good news.
You'd better start the preparations
of your marriage.
I won't even wait for Rogatus to
come back from Constantinople.
I agree.
This marriage has already been late.
You still think that I can marry your
stupid little sister who humiliated me.
Weird.
This castle...
...will not be her home...
...but her grave.
Having Vizier Alamshah here
is fortune.
This is right. He fought the Mongols.
He has been in many wars.
Not only in battlefield, but he also
defeated his enemies in politics.
May Allah keep him with us.
Amen.
Vizier Alam-shah is coming!
Beys of Turkmen tribes, welcome!
Thank you.
Sit down.
You accepted my invitation.
Thank you all.
History is a roaring river.
The ones who build a dam and...
...change its direction will
decide on the history.
We are here to write history in the
name of Seljuqs.
We are here to remove the
misfortune of Turks.
From now on...
...we are going to punish everyone...
...who does business without our
information.
Order brings serenity.
Our Sultan is pleased to have you here.
You are going to be gifted for
your efforts.
The mighty ones of Turkmens...
I fully believe that you'll be loyal.
The only truth is...
...the words of Alamshah.
Our Vizier is generous.
What is this gold for, Vizier Alamshah?
It is the evidence of our seriousness,
Gunduz Bey.
This is given to share to your people.
This is the present you get for
your efforts to provide for your people.
I know you care for your people's wealth,
Gunduz Bey.
This is why I am seeing you
in the name of Kayis.
You'll do what is necessary.
Thank you, Vizier Alamshah.
Thank Allah, we don't need this.
Give this to the needers.
That way, Kayi Tribe will be satisfied.
Ertugrul Ghazi's
bighearted son Gündüz Bey.
What a shame that we haven't met before!
Eyvallah (thank you).
You can't enter with your swords.
Know your limits!
We break the arms reaching to
our swords.
We break the arms of disobeyers
for our state.
Since when one can enter the assembly
with swords, Osman Bey?
Are you going to break the tradition
of your dream state?
Let it go.
Are you bored of living to exceed
your limits?
Wait.
Watch your language.
He is not bored of living.
But he is blind.
Only wolves see a wolf dream.
Do not talk about a dream you cannot see.
We shall kill the cruels...
...who tries to stop us from
reaching to our dream.
We hope that you don't become
one of those cruels.
Now I'll give my sword...
...to my Alp.
Alps!
Your tradition is damaged.
You went through a lot.
For what?
Because of a greedy Bey!
A Bey cannot be greedy!
Being a leader requires an arrogant-free
personailty.
He raids caravans without
assessing the consequences.
He puts Turkmens on the spot.
From now on...
You'll be judged by Konya.
Who are you talking
about Vizier Alam-shah?
Osman Bey.
Salam Aleikum.
(Peace be upon you.)
Alaikum Salam.
(peace be upon you as well.)
Osman Bey.
You accepted my invitation.
Welcome.
Thank you.
Now that everybody is here...
..it is time to give the good news.
However...
...I want to ask you beforehand.
Where are you coming from?
From Inegol.
Some secrets cannot be uncovered by
searching, Osman Bey.
If one doesn't have the capacity and
skills to uncover it...
...you not only wear down yourself,
but also your followers.
When we want to get something...
We get it even if it is behind fifty
doors.
We break all the doors and get it.
Do not worry, Hadrat Vizier.
The doors you break are always open to us.
Here is the good news.
Boran!
Brother!
Are you fine?
Boran Alp is the most loyal of all Alps.
We heard he was captured by the infidels.
As the protector of Turkmen
We could not bear it.
Beys, we have the solution to...
...all of your problems.
Just as we saved Boran Alp
We can solve all your problems as well.
What makes you able to do the things...
...that we cannot Vizier Hazrat?
Might, Turgut Bey, might.
They know enough politics to understand...
...not to treat Seljuk Vizier in the...
...same manner as they would...
a Bey.
Politics...
...is about strengthening the victory...
...won in the battlefield with an ink.
Since no blood was shed
I would like to know about the compromise.
A Seljuk does not compromise
he gives notice period.
And when it's due, he takes what he wants.
Do not worry, Osman Bey.
I said Vizier's presence was a blessing.
He did a good deed may Allah bless him.
- May Allah bless him!
As you can see Osman Bey,
I came here to get things done...
...not to hurt feelings.
Thank you, Vizier Alemshah.
You did not let us down.
Osman Bey is thankful as well.
Thank you, Vizier Alemshah.
I am sure that you will want...
...something in return for this favor.
Come on.
Osman Bey!
From now, no one will do anything...
...without our say.
No raid, no counquest, no compromise...
...will be done without our say.
We'll have peace on guard and walk...
...towards the Mongols.
You assumed I want a return of favor.
I do and that favor is apparent.
Osman Bey
absolute obedience.
We will see.
Boran! Brother are you okay?
Boran?
Brother...
...are you okay?
Thank you my Bey.
I am trying to be fine.
But...
I would expect you to save me from
that ignoble...
...instead of Vizier.
Brother,
What are you saying?
We are coming from Inegol for you.
Every time I got whipped,
while I was starving and thirsty in...
...that dungeon. I had a lot to think
First, poison made her gasp for air,
Shut up!
Then, her veins shattered
Shut your mouth!
You know what kind of pain that is?
A pain...
...you could not believe.
Shut up!
She was crawling...
...and suffering.
My Hatun died...
...for a relic.
That scum killed my Hatun.
I can endure physical pain...
...but my heart is forever wrenched.
Was it worth going thorough all this pain?
For a relic?
My Bey,
do not mind him
he is not in the right frame of mind.
Brother,
the words you are uttering...
...are because of your wounds.
The same feeling you are having.
We will talk later.
Alps
My Bey, excuse me.
Are you alright brother?
Are you alright?
My brother.
What are you doing here brother?
Vizier Alemshah sent the word.
I am here the learn what he wants.
If Allah permits, Boran will be okay.
Whoever does this to my Alps
to Boran
will feel my wrath.
I promise they will feel my wrath...
...in this world and the next.
My Vizier, as you ordered...
...we took Sheik Edebalı
As you thought, he is upset with Osman Bey
Now...
...it is time to visit Edebalı.
Welcome, my Bey.
What happened my Bey?
Vizier Alemshah...
...said that he brought peace and order.
Now that he said that...
...Osman Bey will have to obey him.
What does Osman Bey have to say?
Will he be convinced?
He will Ayşe.
I will convince him.
The situation is clear.
We are in a difficult position.
Turkmen cannot survive...
...a war like this.
Allah forbid, people would be devastated.
Peace is not a choice.
It is an obligation.
May Allah grace our father with the best.
If Allah permits.
Gündüz Bey, may I come in?
You may come in Raşid
My Bey, Osman Bey awaits.
Why has not the Vizier informed us?
He probably has something to do with us.
That is right.
He rounded up the Beys.
He was boasting about giving up Boran.
He wants to damage Kayi's reputation.
What was Gündüz doing there?
May I come in brother?
You may come in brother.
Brother
you were slurring over at the inn.
Now tell me
what were you doing at Vizier's place...
...without informing anyone?
He wanted to see Osman Bey's brother and
invited me to his place.
Should I have said no?
My Gündüz please...
...be careful.
His intentions are unknown as I said...
...when he first came.
He is a two faced conniver.
That is true.
You have to be careful.
You never know when...
...bad things are going to happen.
If Allah permits we'll overcome adversity.
If Allah permits.
For now we wait.
When Sheik Edebalı arrives at Konya
and learns about what is going on...
We will act accordingly.
For now, we need to be patient Osman Bey.
You are hurt pretty badly,
you need to rest.
Dear Sheik Edebalı
you should listen to your healer.
You should stay here until you recover.
We do not know what Koses will do.
Here is safe.
There is no rush I'll wait.
Konur Alp was about to go to Konya anyway.
What a coincidence.
He was about to save you from that ambush
Thank you.
Thank you as well.
We need to inform Osman Bey
Do not worry about that.
You just rest now we'll get it done.
May Allah bless you.
Sir
Why are we keeping Shiek Edebalı here?
If it was up to me I would not give him up
Who would want to hand over...
...their dominance?
Let's wait for a little while.
The thought of Sheik Edebalı getting hurt...
... will worry them to death.
Then we will hand Osman over.
Vizier wants peace.
He wants peace for this soil.
We are tired, beat up...
...and broken
We do not want more trouble.
- I say...
- We will never have peace my brother!
We won't give in the one who
took refugee in us.
I don't know what Vizier's intention is.
I don't trust him
It seems to me that Vizier Alemshah...
...is trying to trick Turkmen Beys
As soon as Sheik Edebalı returns
and learns what is going on
We will take care of Vizier if Allah
permits.
If Allah permits.
We'll take care of him but it's Seljuk
Whoever is a family is a Seljuk,
my daughter.
People are different
We've had traitors among us
without knowing
now think about the government
Mother is right.
People are unpredictable.
We will not show favoritism to anyone
because of their position
When Sheik comes...
we'll decide what we do then.
May I come in my Bey?
You may come in.
My Bey, it's Sheik Edebala
What happened?
He got ambushed on the way to Konya
around Ilgın.
- Calm down!
- My Sheik
My Sheik
He will come do not worry
- Bala
- Osman my father?
Calm down
Göktuğ?
Get the Alps
Get on your horses I want Sheik alive.
Yes my Bey.
Stay calm.
The cinder fell!
This poor Sıddık couldn't become
a blacksmith.
O, the Prophet's friend.
O, the star of the great universe.
O Ebubekir Sıddık, I'd sacrifice my head
for the dust on your feet.
You couldn't stay away from
your friend for a second.
I couldn't be a friend to my friend.
I left him alone in the caves.
I couldn't protect him.
Ah, Kumral, ah!
I left him alone!
I shall die for it!
I am the one who left
Master Hüseyin alone!
I shall die for it!
I'd die for you, O, Muhammed Mustafa!
I couldn't be an Ebubekir!
I couldn't find my friend!
I couldn't save!
I left her alone!
The cinder fell!
May this Kumral burn.
May he burn!
May this Kumral burn!
This poor Sıddık couldn't become
a blacksmith.
The cinder fell.
My Sheik.
Cerkutay.
...we will search this place thoroughly.
We will.
We will find him, brother.
I hope.
Saltuk, send two horses to Söğüt.
We must know the news coming.
Come on.
Alps! Come on!
Continue to search.
I hope Göktuğ will come
with good news, my Bey.
I hope he will, my Bala.
I hope.
Can we enter, my Bey?
Come in, Göktuğ.
My Bey...
...we reached the place of ambush.
There are many traces but they are
all a mess.
We've searched everywhere but...
...we couldn't find my Sheik.
Bala!
Bala, be patient!
Father!
My father!
Thank goodness you are fine!
Thanks to Allah!
My Sheik!
Who did this to you?
Tell me.
The great Edebalı, the light of Oghuz...
...fell into a vile ambush on the road
to Konya.
This doesn't fit such a great
bey like you.
How could you send him to Konya
without precaution, Osman Bey.
Osman Bey.
Sheik Edebalı is here, alive
thanks to Konuralp.
My Sheik, come on.
Bala.
Come on, my Sheik.
Who did this to my Sheik?
Tell me.
Whoever you hurt did it.
Kosses.
We all know why.
Those who hurt Edebalı today,
may do worse tomorrow.
They won't stop until they take Mari.
Things will get ugly...
...if you don't give Kosses
his sister back.
People will get hurt.
The order will be broken.
A wise bey like you...
...will do the right thing.
What needs to be done is obvious.
Mari, who took refuge from us...
...will not be delivered to them
until we are dead.
Truth is a two-winged bird.
One of them is Qur'an and
the other is tradition.
Both of them order this.
There it is.
Stubbornness.
Every word we say is...
...for the sake of Turks.
Do you take responsibility for what
will happen to Turks...
...Osman Bey?
Turgut Bey.
What about you?
Gündüz Bey, the oldest of the Kayıs.
What do you say?
I can't say a word over my Bey.
Consider this well.
I give you until tomorrow for
your decision.
What you need to do is
to respect the peace.
This doesn't seem pleasant, Osman Bey.
The best is that I take Mari
and return to my tribe.
Mari is with us from now on.
You are with us too.
This is very nice of you.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
However, everyone will get
hurt because of me.
Let me go. I don't want to get
you in more trouble.
I'll go to my tribe and prepare
for battle.
What battle?
A battle is a celebration for us.
But don't get confused.
If he gave us time....
...then we will share our decision...
...by inviting them to the wedding.
Make the arrangements!
You and Mari have a wedding.
Ah, Osman Bey!
You supported me in these hard times.
The place doesn't matter.
The Bey you have does.
I saw you when I met you.
From now on, you are my Bey.
Every time you take your sword out...
...it will be my sword.
Your road is my road.
And the life I have is a servant
for that road.
From now on...
...only death can separate us, Osman Bey.
My Yonca.
The poison first took her breath...
...then her veins fell apart!
Do you know what kind of pain that is?
It is such a pain that...
...you can't believe it.
She died agonizedly.
Yonca!
My Boran!
My boy!
Boran, my boy!
Kumral Abdal.
This pain doesn't go away.
It doesn't.
Don't be like this, my Boran.
Don't be like this.
May their hands break!
Kumral Abdal.
This, here hurts.
Don't do this, my Boran.
Don't do this.
I can't live without her!
What did I tell you, Boran?
This trial is tough.
You think you can't survive
it but you do.
You are here in front of me, alive.
This is a false world.
A world with no promised tomorrow.
Don't be deceived by it, my Boran.
This was a green tree yesterday.
It dried.
False world.
Flowers fade.
Fire blows out.
People die.
When the time comes, everything goes.
Gonca is gone.
Allah called her, and she left.
What do you do?
You say you died.
You will get through, my Boran.
You will live as you are hurt.
You will live and be patient.
In the name of Allah.
Your wound is severe.
The healing is given in your Rabb's words.
Turn to your Rabb.
In the name of Allah.
Make your Gonca live here.
Read lots of Qur'an.
Can we enter?
Come in.
How do I look?
You look beautiful.
Stunning.
Bala Hatun gave this to me.
Thank her.
Can we?
Mari.
I should've said this before.
But everything happened so fast.
When I first saw you,
I told myself that...
...this girl will get me
into many trouble.
You did.
But everything seemed pleasant...
...since you were with me.
This won't be easy.
Which love is easy?
I am all in, if you are with me.
Will you be the possessor of my heart...
...my partner for life, Mari?
As long as you are with me...
...I can bear anything, Turgut.
Call Gündüz Bey.
I want to talk to him about
something important.
But warn him.
Osman shouldn't know it.
Inform Kosses that Mari will be delivered.
As you order.
Write. To our Sultan.
The great Sultan of four seasons...
...here, where I work as your shadow...
...my word doesn't effect Osman Bey...
...son of Ertuğrul Gazi.
This noble servant of yours...
...who considers disobedience...
...as the glory of being a bey...
...is trading with...
...Sagarus, the governer of İznik.
The sea of ​​heedlessness he is in
is so wide that...
...he is keeping the sister of
Harmankaya Governor...
...Lord Kosses as a hostage.
The moves he make are no good for
the Seljuk...
... and you, my Sultan.
I am afraid that the presence of this rebel named Osman...
...will get us crashed between the Moghuls
Rumelians, and Kayseri.
My actual fear is that he may not settle
for being a Bey...
...and try to establish a new state.
All these troubles he caused are...
...because of his ambition.
It is necessary to put him in the dungeon
and give him the sentence.
May Allah give us...
...what is the best for us...
...and make it happen.
May Allah give our Great Sultan...
...an endless life of rule.
This will go with a pigeon.
It must reach the Sultan before
the ink on it dries.
I didn't get the chance to ask.
It is about the state.
Even if you ask, I say it's a secret.
Right.
He just came. Why is he sending...
...his most loyal soldier to Konya?
My Sheik...
...who else knew you were to meet
the Sultan except you and me?
How would that dog Kosses know the road?
It was no secret we were going to Konya.
Out aim was the secret.
Do you suspect anyone, Osman Bey?
Konuralp being there, then...
Obviously he knew that he'd got into
trouble when he arrived in Konya.
I will send one of my Alps after him.
We must know what he is up to.
There is no price for a word
if we don't have proof.
The truth will come out sooner or later.
One must try too.
I will go to Konya again
as soon as possible.
His game will be out in the open
when I arrive in Konya.
Those who want to lead must defeat
their arrogance first.
Gündüz Bey, you are so not
yourself that...
... you even gave up on your
rightful place.
Vizier Alemşah, if your plan is
to start a fight in Kayı...
...you are not in the right place.
My aim is not separation, it's unity.
Gathering all the Turks under
the flag of Great Seljuk.
For this, we need steadiness.
Your brother is hurting this steadiness.
Since when conquering is hurting?
We don't have our old power.
Moguls wrecked us.
If Konya falls, you will fall too.
It is not the time to fight
with the Rumelians.
For a woman?
This is tradition. We won't give those
who need our help up.
The tradition is to act
for the sake of the state.
Tradition is fighting...
...for the safety of the people.
It is acting accordingly.
This is the tradition.
It is not watching the tribe burn...
...for a woman.
The message coming from Rumelia.
Rogatus is in Constantine now.
They are building an army.
They will bury all the tribes
to the ground.
What should we do now?
We will do the lesser evil, Gündüz Bey.
Alps...
...go!
-Good luck!
-Thank you. Welcome.
I have great fabrics.
This one.
This is nice too.
It is beautiful.
This will look great on my gorgeous girl.
I don't know how to thank you.
You care for me as I am
your own daughter, sister.
There is no as. You are our own
from now on.
You are our sister now, like every
other girl in tribe.
If you are becoming a wife
of a Turk Bey...
...let me tell you about our customs.
Mother?
-Come on. Get them ready for us.
-Sure.
Come here girl.
-Good luck.
-Thank you.
We put some honey in the bride's
mouth so she will talk sweetly.
What are you doing?
I am just learning.
We have a wedding soon.
Mashallah to my son!
Thank you, mother.
I should learn these.
Come on, leave.
Don't bother us!
I will teach you later.
Selcen Mother, you said honey
for talking sweetly, right?
Yes, son. But you don't
need it.
We'll give it to who
needs it.
Come on, mother. Let us buy corn.
Let's buy it.
So that your tent and tribe
be in prosperity.
But let's buy a lot.
You'll need it.
Aygül, my girl. Take care of
this.
We'll take care of the others.
Come on.
Give me one puch, brother.
Why are you buying corn, mad girl?
For this, Cerkutay, mad boy.
Come on, move. Move.
Alps!
The greatest Sultan of seven regions
and four seasons.
On these borders that I stand as
your shadow...
my words don't have effect on the
border bey...
named Osman, son of Ertuğrul.
He even holds Harmankaya's lord Michael
Kosses' sister...
as hostage.
His actions are against...
the Seljuks and you, our sultan.
He must be put in a dungeon
and trialed at once.
Osman Bey, how can you do this?
I've given you my armies back then.
You ruined my trust for you.
It's the sultan's order.
That rebel named Osman will be arrested
and brought to me.
It's been a long while since
seeing you this happy, my bey.
May Allah keep your happiness.
Thank you.
But it's your turn, Kutan.
Remember that.
-Inshallah, my bey.
-Inshallah.
And it's good that we united with
Kayı Tribe, my bey.
It is.
From now, both our weapons and
our hearts...
will be under Osman Bey's order.
Mashallah!
Everyone is happy out there.
All the folks are waiting for the wedding.
We'll take care of it with
Allah's approval.
You are giving us a debt that
can't be repaid.
Our responsibility shouldn't be a
debt for you.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
What's wrong, brother?
Where are you coming from?
From Söğüt, Osman Bey.
What were you doing in Söğüt?
The things we always do, Osman Bey.
I took a walk and returned.
I've things to do. I'll proceed if you
allow me, Osman Bey.
Proceed, brother.
Proceed.
Osman...
Harmankaya Castle
Please, stop, Nikola!
I'm out of patience, Kosses.
I see that, Nikola.
But don't worry, the vizier will
keep his word.
He'll bring us Mari.
I brought Vizier Alemşah's regards.
The vizier said that he'll give
you Mari.
Good.
Tell Vizier Alemşah that we are
grateful.
Finally...
Mari is coming!
So, my friend.
When are we making the wedding?
Right away. Right away, Kosses.
I won't make you regret it.
I'll take good care of good Mari.
I'll give her heaven in this world.
Kosses is worse than a rabid dog!
He even touched Sheik Edebali!
Problems are coming one after other...
and I can't convince Osman.
To save the people from Kosses' cruelty...
I don't want it but...
we must give Mari to the vizier, Ayşe.
Gündüz. How could that happen?
How can you return a refugee?
Isn't there any other way?
I've searched for a thousand
solutions, Ayşe!
A thousand!
No!
The emperor is gathering an army.
The lords are angry, the Seljuks are
after us. And my brother...
My brother is after heroism!
We'll take care of this without letting
anyone hear it.
For the good of the people.
If I didn't believe you, I would hand you
over myself.
My husband...
I know the purity of your intentions.
But what if Osman Bey hears it?
What will he say?
How will we explain it?
We'll take care of it without
letting him hear it.
No one will hear anything, Ayşe.
Is it for Mari?
When she drinks it, she'll pass out.
Find a way to make her drink it.
I'll take her out of the
tribe secretly.
Ayşe, it's for our tribe.
It's for the people.
Would I do this?
It's for our tribe.
How was your day in Söğüt?
It was so good!
Good.
Are we getting married tomorrow?
Yes, you are marrying this man that
you once called a barbarian.
May I enter, my girl?
Come in.
Turgut?
What are you doing here, son?
I've come to talk.
To see if she needs anything.
What are you going to talk about?
You've spoken enough and
convinced her to marry.
What else will you say, son?
Go. You won't enter this tent
until tomorrow.
Go.
As you order, mother.
Come on, son.
Look, he is still here!
I'm leaving, mother.
Come.
My daughter, you burned
his heart well.
Mother.
Come.
Mari.
Sit.
Mashallah.
We took so many things.
I've been carrying it all.
It's hard to be a woman.
Soon, Aygül.
We heard that your turn will come.
Bala.
My daughter, they'll fit you well.
Thank you.
Ayşe Hatun, come in.
Come on now, let's open it.
Mother, look how beautiful they are.
They are really beautiful.
This one will look good on you.
They are all pretty. Look at the
colors of this one.
Do you like it, Mari.
They are beautiful.
Osman Bey's rat.
What did you want to find
by coming after us?
Konur.
His bones are itching.
Beat him until you are out of
strength.
Don't worry.
Everything will be done tomorrow.
Inshallah, Osman Bey.
Inshallah.
I know what you are doing for me.
I can't repay you.
Thank you.
Brother, we don't know what the heathens
are up to.
For that reason, tell the alps...
they should be on guard
every moment.
Even a bird won't fly over the tribe.
But...
I don't want any mistakes.
As you order, my bey.
With the name of Allah.
My bey, what's the name of this?
They call it opium.
Shh.
Don't.
What if this thing hurts Mari?
No.
It will only make her pass out.
And also, it's not just for Mari.
Yes?
No one should know it.
No one should hear it.
Alps.
Alps shouldn't see it either.
Alps?
What can we do?
To get rid of a big trouble...
it's a small one.
There is no other way.
Aygül Hatun will give meal to
the alps.
We'll give the sherbet.
So that they won't stand in my way.
May Allah help us, my bey.
I hope we can do it without being seen.
We'll take care of it.
We'll take care of it, inshallah.
For the good of the tribe,
there no other ways.
Let us be the bad ones.
If you say it's for the good of
the people...
Allah knows our intentions.
True.
The cart is ready.
You make Mari drink the sherbet.
Make sure that the alps also drink it.
Inshallah no one will stand in my way.
Don't worry, my bey.
We'll take Mari out without
being noticed.
My wife.
Give me your blessing.
It's yours, my bey.
May I enter, my bey?
Come in.
My bey.
Someone else needs to follow the
vizier now.
I was exposed, my bey.
They know me now.
I couldn't succeed.
Who did this?
The vizier?
Saltuk!
Yes, my bey.
The meal smells so good.
What's in it?
Yours has poison.
It's the first time I'm eating a
poison that is sweeter than honey.
Allah bless your hands.
Sherbet is really good too.
Ayşe Hatun made it.
Enjoy your meals.
-Thank you, sister Aygül.
-Thank you, Aygül Hatun.
Enjoy your meals, alps.
Thank you, Gündüz Bey.
Göktuğ, where are the other alps?
They are helping the people
for the feast.
Good. Good.
Gather the rest of the alps.
Warriors, it's Osman Bey's order.
We'll increase caution around the tribe.
As you order, my bey.
Enjoy it.
You will be so beautiful, Mari.
Thank you.
Same to you, Aygül.
Her time is soon.
Cerkutay is fast.
When Turgut Bey sees you, he'll fall
in love again.
Ayşe Hatun.
She'll look so good, right?
You will look so good, Mari.
You'll be like a fairy.
What's that, Ayşe Hatun?
I made sherbet.
I prepared for you too.
But I sent them to Malhun Hatun's
tent, thinking you had left.
Tomorrow will be a long day.
Mari needs to rest.
Right?
Ayşe is right, ladies.
It's late now.
Good night, Mari.
Good night.
Thank you.
Enjoy it, Mari.
Good night.
Gündüz.
You do it for your tribe, Gündüz.
Ayşe.
Ayşe, what did you do?
Mari...
drank the sherbet.
Good.
Good. Head alps also drank it.
When they sleep, it will be easier.
Boran wasn't there.
He never left his tent.
Tomorrow morning, I'll give Mari to
the vizier's men.
Gündüz.
Ayşe!
Ayşe, I beg you!
We aren't doing evil.
We are doing it for all the
Turkmen tribes.
May I enter?
May Allah forgive me.
What is this, Vizier Alemşah?
We've done many things since
we came.
Which one are you asking, Osman Bey?
Vizier!
It's Saltuk!
How can you beat a border bey's
alp?
That's why he is breathing now.
If it was someone else...
I would hang him at the entrance
of Söyüt as an example.
The one who hits my alps pays!
There are many things to pay for, Osman!
You tell me first.
What does it mean to have a statesman
followed?
Who are you to have me followed?
I'm the owner of Söğüt,
the borders...
the tribe, the diwan you sit on and
even the bed you lay on!
You are speaking over your strength,
Osman Bey.
This belongs to the Seljuks.
This belongs to the state!
Here, I'm the bey and the state!
This rebellion, this attitude...
you prepared your own end, Osman.
But this is your last revolt.
You put the shackles on your hands.
Gündüz Bey will bring the girl in
the morning.
It's the end of Osman, Konur.
Where am I?
Who are you?
Stop!
What are you doing?
Help!
Where am I?
Gündüz Bey. The vizier sent his regards.
Soldiers.
Come on.
Brothers, wake up.
Gencebey!
Get up.
Cerkutay!
Wake up!
Brothers, how did we sleep
like this?
Thanks to Aygül Hatun.
We ate a lot.
Get up, Cerkutay.
Aygül.
Dowey.
Speak, Aygül Hatun.
Why are you here?
Aygül! Dowery?
Yes. Yes. The dowery.
The dowery.
And you say that I eat like a bear.
You all have a Cerkutay in you.
May I enter, Mari?
Mari?
Where is she?
Malhun.
The bed is untouched.
The veil is where I left it.
Turgut!
Yes, mother.
Son!
Mari, do you know where she is?
I don't.
Isn't she here?
She was in her tent
yesterday when we left.
But the bed and
the veil over it are untouched.
It's just as I left it.
We checked everywhere.
But she isn't anywhere.
How so?
Malhun. Who is absent?
Mari, my bey.
Osman Bey.
What is this?
Where can she go?
My Mari wouldn't go without telling.
How?
It's a huge tribe, son. We are all here.
They can't kidnap her.
How can that happen, Osman Bey?
Where can Mari go?
Who could do that?
Who?
Alps!
Tell me!
Hasn't anyone seen her leaving?
Nikola...
my bey, it must be Nikola.
Nikola!
Turgut Bey, wait!
It's not the time to wait, Osman Bey.
The scoundrels kidnapped
her in the night.
Come on, alps!
We are leaving!
Alps!
Come on!
We are in a hurry, my vizier.
What is it about?
Soldiers.
The Seljuk Sultan...
Sultan Mesud ordered your arrest,
Osman Bey.
What are you saying?
Do you know what you say?
He is Osman Bey, the bey of the Kayı!
It's Sultan Mesud's order.
You are under arrest, Osman Bey.
Why are you arresting him?
Speak!
Osman.
Alps.
Lower your weapons.
Take off your hands!
Don't touch my weapon.
Leave him.
He isn't healthy. He has
suffered enough.
Mother.
Come.
İnegöl Castle
Finally, Kosses...
finally.
Take good care of her, Nikola.
Whatever mistake she makes,
she is my sister.
She is my most valuable.
Don't make her sad.
Ever.
Never.
Don't worry.
I'll take good care of her.
Mari.
You...
my dear wife!
Welcome.
Damn it.
How can you do this to me?
My God!
Mari, you are driving me mad!
Look at yourself!
I'll make you pay for this!
Turgut won't leave me here.
Enough, I said.
I hate you, brother!
Mari is my wife now.
Watch your actions.
Cornellia, you are my guest now.
Comfort yourself.
Those who do this to us...
who knows what they are doing
to Osman Bey.
His intention is to take my bey
out of these lands.
He acts like doing good...
but he is evil.
Osman Bey's loyal alps!
I wish you chose obedience
to your state...
over loyalty to your bey.
Now, you wouldn't be suffering.
Vizier.
Your cruelty isn't enough to make
the Kayı's alps give up.
Don't hold back.
Soldiers!
Whip them until you separate
their flesh from bones!
Then, throw them to
the dungeon!
You go to Söğüt.
Inform Vizier Alemşah.
As you order.
We can't answer the Sultan
nor the Vizier!
If you come before finding
Osman, you'll lose your head!
Snake! I knew he would
do something!
He has been meddling with my
bey since he came.
I knew it.
I said it the day he arrived.
His eyes look like Saadettin Köpek.
Will we stay here, mother?
What should we do?
We won't wait, Bala!
The vizier will pay for this.
What did I do?
I trusted the vizier and do what?
They took my brother.
Osman Bey isn't guilty.
They can't do anything.
Right?
I don't know, Ayşe.
Anything!
But I will find out.
I'll go to Alemşah.
What will we do, my bey?
We'll enter the castle and take
Mari out.
Would I leave Mari to
Nikola?
How will we get pass all
the soldiers, my bey?
You know, Nikola is protected well.
We'll enter in a way that...
all the world will talk about it.
Hang on, Mari.
Hang on.
May I enter, my vizier.
Come in.
My vizier, Gündüz Bey is here.
Let him in.
Vizier Alemşah.
Are you involved in this?
It's Sultan Mesud's order.
We follow any order coming
from Konya.
May I enter, my vizier.
Come in.
My vizier, news from Konur Alp.
Osman Bey...
What happened to Osman Bey?
Speak!
Osman Bey ran away, my vizier.
We don't know how it happened.
Your brother's revolts don't end,
Gündüz Bey.
Your brother doesn't listen to you,
or to the vizier.
Now, he doesn't listen to the sultan!
No, I don't know what he's trying
to do this time.
This isn't good.
Inform the sultan.
Inform him that...
Osman ran away from trial. He is
a rebel.
Send criers.
Osman's revolt should be heard
by everyone.
His people will hear how
he betrayed the Seljuks.
He'll get caught at sight.
As you order, my vizier.
Vizier Alemşah.
Do you need to make it heard?
We don't do anything without
a reason.
Return to your tribe.
Kayı Tribe isn't a tribe to leave
without a leader.
Prepare, Gündüz Bey.
You will sit on the fur throne.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com